Guide to the Arthur M. Schlesinger, Jr. papers, 1922-2007
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series I: Correspondence, 1923-2007; 384760; 286 boxes
  - Subseries I.A. Alphabetical correspondence, 1934-2006; 384761; 150 boxes
    - Cas-Chan, 384856 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Castro, Fidel, 2000-2005; 384857 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Cel-Chr, 384858 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Cha-Chi, 384859 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Cha-Chuv, 384860 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Chayefsky, Paddy, 1959-1961; 384861 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Chelsea House, 1966-2003; 384862
      - History Machine Series, 384863 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Legal, 384864 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
      - General, 384865 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Chiffriller, Mary, 1967-1992; 384866 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Cho-Cog, 384867 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Christopher, Warren, 2001; 384868 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Chu-Coff, 384869 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Churchill, Winston Jr., 2003; 384870 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Ci-Cz, 384871 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Committee for New York City, 1975; 384872 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - City University of New York Presidential Search Committee, 1972-1973; 384873 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Cl-Com, 384874 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Cla-Cli, 384875 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Clark, Joseph S., 1966-1980, 1988; 384876 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Clinton, Bill, 1987-2001; 384877 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Cog-Coy, 384878 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Coh-Cop, 384879 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Cohen, Benjamin V., 1951-1988; 384880 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Collins, Gail, 384881 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Commager, Henry Steele, 1966-1994; 384882 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Committee for Public Justice, 1972-1974; 384883 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Committee to Save the American History Room, 1980-1982; 384884 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Condon, Richard, 384885 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Coo-Cz, 384886 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Cor-Cum, 384887 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Corcoran, Thomas G., 1982; 384888 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1967-1976; 384889 (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
    - Cowan, Lester, 1966; 384890 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Cra-Cz, 384891 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Cun-Day, 384892 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Cunliffe, Marcus, 1966-1990; 384893 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - D, 384894 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
    - Da-Del, 384895 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Da-Dh, 384896 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Dab-Day, 384897 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Dallek, Robert, 2002; 384898 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Danner, Blythe, 2003; 384899 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - De-Di, 384900 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Dea-Die, 384901 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Dean, Howard, 2005; 384902 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Deg-Dig, 384903 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Advisory Council, 1975; 384904 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Deutsch, Andre, 1966-1990; 384905 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - DeVoto, Bernard, 1944-1997; 384906 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Di-Dz, 384907 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Dickinson, Angie, 2003; 384908 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Dietrich, Marlene, 1961; 384909 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Dif-Dou, 384910 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Diggins, Jack, 1971-1994; 384911 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Dii-Diz, 384912 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Dillon, C. Douglas, 2001; 384913 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Do-Doy, 384914 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Dob-Dow, 384915 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Doctorow, E.L., 2001; 384916 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Douglas, Paul H., 1966-1976; 384917 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Dow-Dy, 384918 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Doy-Dys, 384919 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Dra-Dz, 384920 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Draper, Theodore, 1961; 384921 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Duchess of Devonshire, 2002; 384922 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Dukakis, Michael, 1974-1988; 384923 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Dungan, Ralph A., 1966-1970; 384924 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Dutton, Fred, 1966-1978; 384925 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - E, 384926 (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
    - E-Ell, 384927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Ea-Em, 384928 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Ea-Ex, 384929 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Eban, Suzy (Mrs. Abba), 2002; 384930 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Edelstein, Julius, 1966-1994; 384931 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - El-Ey, 384932 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Emmet, 1949-1956; 384933 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - En-Ez, 384934 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Evans, Rowland, 1966-1978; 384935 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - F, 384936 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
    - F-Fey, 384937 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Fa-Fit, 384938 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Fa-Fl, 384939 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Fa-Fol, 384940 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Fairbank, John K., 1966-1994; 384941 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Farrell, James T., 1966-1979; 384942 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1950-1951; 384943 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Feiffer, Jules, 2002; 384944 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Feis, Herbert, 1966-1973, 1984; 384945 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Fi-Fl, 384946 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Fi-Fra, 384947 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Fia-Fz, 384948 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Finletter, Thomas K., 1966-1982; 384949 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Fitzgerald, Carol, 1983-1993; 384950 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Fla-Fras, 384951 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Fleming, Mary, 1937; 384952 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Fon-Fra, 384953 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Fox, Judge John J., 1966-1983; 384954 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1935-1957; 384955 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Fraser, Antonia, 2002; 384956 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Fraz-Fy, 384957 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Fre-Fur, 384958 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Fre-Fz, 384959 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Fritchey, Clayton, 1966-1991; 384960 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Fuentes, Carlos, 2004; 384961 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1966-1992; 384962 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Fund of America, 1969-1970; 384963 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - G, 384964 (Box 47, Folder 1-3)
    - G-Gay, 384965 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - G-Gk, 384966 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Ga-Gav, 384967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Ga-Gh, 384968 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Ga-Gi, 384969 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Galbraith, J. Alan, 2006; 384970 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1965-2006; 384971 (Box 49, Folder 2-4)
    - Galbraith Dinner (11/17/69), 384972 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Galea, Mrs. J.M., 1989-1994; 384973 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Gardner, Richard N., 1967-1994; 384974 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Geb-Giv, 384975 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Geyl, Pieter, 1960-1961; 384976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Gi-Gz, 384977 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Gl-Goo, 384978 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Gl-Gor, 384979 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Gl-Gra, 384980 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Goldsmith, William M., 1972-1987; 384981 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1959; 384982 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Goodwin, Richard N., 1966-1994; 384983 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Gor-Gra, 384984 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Gos-Gri, 384985 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Graham, Katharine, 1961-1992; 384986 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Gre-Gri, 384987 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Gre-Gro, 384988 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Gro-Gy, 384989 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Gro-Gz, 384990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Gru-Gy, 384991 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Guare, John, 2005; 384992 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Gurney, A. R., 2004; 384993 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - H, 384994 (Box 55, Folder 1-4)
    - Ha-Hap, 384995 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Ha-Hh, 384996 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Haa-Hap, 384997 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Haa-Har, 384998 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Halsted, Anna, 1966; 384999 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Har, 385000 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Hara-Harw, 385001 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Harding, Raymond, 1979-1983; 385002 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Harlech, Lord, 1970-1987; 385003 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Harlech Scholars Trust, 1985-1993; 385004 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Harr-Harw, 385005 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Harriman, Averell, 1948-1993; 385006 (Box 58, Folder 1-4)
    - Harris, Seymour, 1964-1977; 385007 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Hartwell, Mrs. William Michael Berry, Baroness, 1968-1982; 385008 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Harvard University, 1946-1961; 385009 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Harvard University Library, 1950-1955; 385010 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Has-Hei, 385011 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Hays, Brooks, 1966-1981; 385012 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - He-Hew, 385013 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - He-Hey, 385014 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Heckscher, August, 1967-1994; 385015 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Hefner, Christie, 385016 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Hel-Hl, 385017 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Hi-Hz, 385018 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Hi-Hol, 385019 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Hickok, Lorena, 1966; 385020 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Hig-Hop, 385021 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Hill and Barlow, 385022
      - 1968-1972, 385023 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
      - General, 385024 (Box 63, Folder 1-4)
    - Ho-Hor, 385025 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Ho-Hz, 385026 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Hob-Hoo, 385027 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Hogan, Elizabeth, 1985-1991; 385028 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Holbrooke, Richard, 385029 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Hoopes, Townsend, 1966-1976; 385030 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Hor-Hy, 385031 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Horne, Alistair, 1979-1994; 385032 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Hos-Hy, 385033 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Houghton Mifflin, 385034
      - Editors, 1965-1982; 385035 (Box 66, Folder 1-5)
      - General, 1956-2000; 385036 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, 1965-1978, 1986; 385037 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - I, 385038 (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
    - I-Jam, 385039 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - I-Jay, 385040 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Inter-American Foundation for the Arts, 1966-1967, 1981; 385041 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Interplay, 1967-1970; 385042 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - J, 385043 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
    - Jab-Jay, 385044 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Jan-Ju, 385045 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Janeway, Elliot and Elizabeth, 1966-1969; 385046 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Je-Jz, 385047 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Jeb-Jus, 385048 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Jenkins, Jennifer, 2005; 385049 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Jenkins, Lord, 2001; 385050 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Jenkins, Roy, 1966-1994; 385051 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1966-1976; 385052 (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
    - John F. Kennedy Foundation, 1968; 385053 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - John F. Kennedy Presidential Library and Museum, 385054
      - 1964-1978, 385055 (Box 72, Folder 2-4)
      - 1979-1981, 385056 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Oral History Project, 1969-1972; 385057 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, 2001; 385058 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, Luci, 1965; 385059 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, Lyndon, 1958, 1965; 385060 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Johnston, Thomas M.C., Jr., 1968-1974; 385061 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Lee, 1987-1988; 385062 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - K, 385063 (Box 73, Folder 8-11)
    - K-Kem, 385064 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Ka-Kem, 385065 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Kah-Kay, 385066 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Kahn, Herman, 1966-1977; 385067 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Kea-Key, 385068 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Keesing's, 1952-1954; 385069 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Ken-Kil, 385070 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Ken-Kk, 385071 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Kennan, George, 1966-1994; 385072 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, Edward, 1997-2006; 385073 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, Ethel, 1970-1999; 385074 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy, Joan, 1969-1978; 385075 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1957; 385076 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy, John F., Jr., 1998; 385077 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy, Joseph II, 1969-1970; 385078 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, Joseph III, 1972; 385079 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1965-1969; 385080 (Box 77, Folder 5-7)
    - Kennedy, Rose, 1966-1978; 385081 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Kerr, Barbara, 1992-1996; 385082 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Kh-Kon, 385083 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Kim-Ky, 385084 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1998, 2004; 385085 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Kl-Kz, 385086 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., 1966-1994; 385087 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Koch, Edward, 1998; 385088 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Koo-Kup, 385089 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Kur-Lan, 385090 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - L, 385091 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
    - La-Lan, 385092 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - La-Laz, 385093 (Box 80, Folder 4-5)
    - La-Ln, 385094 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Ladjevardi, Habib, 1969-1980; 385095 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Landon, Alf M., 1961-1986; 385096 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Lap-Lee, 385097 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Lawford, Patricia Kennedy, 1975-1985; 385098 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Le-Lez, 385099 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Lea-Ll, 385100 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Lef-Ley, 385101 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Lerner, Max, 1948; 385102 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Anthony, 385103 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Li-Liv, 385104 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Lib-Ll, 385105 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Library of America, 1982-1983; 385106 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Lindsay, John V., 1966-1994; 385107 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Lo-Ly, 385108 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Lo-Lz, 385109 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Loc-Luk, 385110 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Lodge, George, 2004; 385111 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Loe-Lz, 385112 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Lord, Walter, 1967-1992; 385113 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Lun-Ly, 385114 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Lurer, Bonnie H., 1971-1975; 385115 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - M, 385116 (Box 86, Folder 5-6)
    - M, 385117 (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
    - Ma-Mh, 385118 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Ma-Mac, 385119 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Ma-McT, 385120 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1955-1977; 385121 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - McA-McCar, 385122 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - McA-McZ, 385123 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - McCarthy, Eugene, 1968, 1978; 385124 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - McCarthy, Mary, 1949-1961, 1982; 385125 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - McCas-McD, 385126 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - McCormick, Ken, 1966-1982; 385127 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - McE-McW, 385128 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - McGovern, George, 1966-2001; 385129 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
    - McNamara, Robert, 2003, 2006; 385130 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Mad-Man, 385131 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Mad-Marx, 385132 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Maddox, Robert James, 1970-1989; 385133 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Mailer, Norman, 2005; 385134 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Man-Marcy, 385135 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Manning, Robert J., 1966-1979; 385136 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Mansfield, Mike, 1961; 385137 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Marc-Marz, 385138 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Mard-Marz, 385139 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Martin, John Bartlow, 1966-1992; 385140 (Box 92, Folder 5-6)
    - Marx, Groucho, 1960-1961; 385141 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Mas-Maz, 385142 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Mas-Mey, 385143 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Mazo, Jay, 1969-1970; 385144 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Me-Mic, 385145 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Mes-Mey, 385146 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Mi-Mz, 385147 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Mia-Miz, 385148 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Mid-Mil, 385149 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Mid-Mis, 385150 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Miller, Arthur, 2004; 385151 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Perry, 1939; 385152 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Minow, Newton, 1998; 385153 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Mirren, Helen, 385154 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Mit-Moo, 385155 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Moa-Mor, 385156 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Mor-Morr, 385157 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Mor-My, 385158 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Mor-Myr, 385159 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Morgenthau, Robert, 2004; 385160 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Morris, Robert, 1973-1974, 1982-1983; 385161 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Mos-Mz, 385162 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1973-1994; 385163 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1966-1998; 385164 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Murtha, John P., 2006; 385165 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - N, 385166 (Box 98, Folder 1-2)
    - Na-New, 385167 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Nab-Nes, 385168 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Nab-Nic, 385169 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Nabokov, Nicolas, 1959-1984; 385170 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - National Historical Publications Committee, 1972-1981; 385171 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - National Society of Film Critics, 1970-1972; 385172 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Negotiation Now!, 1967-1968; 385173 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Neu-Nieb, 385174 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - New Class Study, 1977-1978; 385175 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - New Democrat, 1969-1972; 385176 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - New York City Bicentennial Corporation, 1973-1975; 385177 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - New York Public Library, 1972-1982; 385178 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Newman, Paul, 1998; 385179 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Ng-Nut, 385180 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Nie-Ny, 385181 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold and Ursula, 1949-1960; 385182 (Box 100, Folder 4-5)
    - Niel-Ny, 385183 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - O, 385184 (Box 101, Folder 2-4)
    - O-Ok, 385185 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Oa-Ok, 385186 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - O'Brien, Edna, 1999; 385187 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - O'Donnell, Kenny, 1961; 385188 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Ol-Oz, 385189 (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, 1962-1967; 385190 (Box 102, Folder 3-6)
    - Organizations, 1983-1994; 385191 (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
    - Organizations, 1983-1994; 385192 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - P-Q, 385193 (Box 104, Folder 2-4)
    - Pa-Par, 385194 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Paar, Jack, 1960; 385195 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Pac-Pay, 385196 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Pac-Pes, 385197 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Papers of Woodrow Wilson, 1966-1969; 385198 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Pas-Pep, 385199 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Pea-Pes, 385200 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Penguin Press, 385201
      - New American History Series, 2003; 385202 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - General, 2003-2005; 385203 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - Per-Phi, 385204 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Pet-Pl, 385205 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Pet-Plu, 385206 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Pia-Pit, 385207 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Pinter, Harold, 2001-2002; 385208 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Pla-Pol, 385209 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Plimpton, George, 2003; 385210 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Poc-Pur, 385211 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Pom-Put, 385212 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Pog-Pre, 385213 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Pri-Py, 385214 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Prichard, Edward, 1985-1991; 385215 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Proshansky, Dr. Harold M., 1968-1978; 385216 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Pulitzer Prize History Jury, 1975-1976; 385217 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Q, 385218 (Box 110, Folder 3-4)
    - Q-Ree, 385219 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - R, 385220 (Box 110, Folder 6-8)
    - Ra-Ray, 385221 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Ra-Rn, 385222 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Rab-Ray, 385223 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Radiotelevisione Italiana, 1967-1977; 385224 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Rauh, Joseph L., Jr., 1961-1994; 385225 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Rauh, Joseph L., Jr., 1961-1994; 385226 (Box 112, Folder 1-5)
    - Re-Riz, 385227 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Rec-Rey, 385228 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Redgrave, Vanessa, 2004; 385229 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Redstone, Sumner, 1998; 385230 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Reg-Rig, 385231 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Revitalization Corps, 1966-1972; 385232 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Rib-Rod, 385233 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Ril-Roc, 385234 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Ro-Roo, 385235 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Ro-Rz, 385236 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Robert F. Kennedy Action Corps, 1971-1983; 385237 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David, 2005; 385238 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Rod-Ros, 385239 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Rog-Rosen, 385240 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Roger Baldwin Foundation, 1967-1968; 385241 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Rooney, Andy, 2003; 385242 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1961; 385243 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Ros-Rost, 385244 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Rot-Ruh, 385245 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Rot-Ry, 385246 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Roth, Philip, 2004; 385247 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Rovere, Richard, 1951-1991; 385248 (Box 116, Folder 4-6)
    - Rowe, James, Jr., 1966-1983; 385249 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Ru-Ry, 385250 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Rum-Ry, 385251 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - S, 385252 (Box 117, Folder 3-6)
    - S, 385253 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Sa-Sal, 385254 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Sa-Say, 385255 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Sa-Sg, 385256 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Sac-Say, 385257 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Salinas De Gortari, Carlos, 2002; 385258 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Salinger, Pierre, 1966-1993; 385259 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Sam-Schm, 385260 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Saturday Review, 1977-1980; 385261 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Sb-Schw, 385262 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Sca-Sch, 385263 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Sch-Sel, 385264 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Schiff, Karenna Gore, 2006; 385265 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Schn-Sg, 385266 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Sco-Sey, 385267 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Scott, Hugh, 1962; 385268 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Seigenthaler, John, 1981-1992; 385269 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Seldes, Gilbert and Marian, 1965-1986, 1998; 385270 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Sen-Sh, 385271 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Sf-Sif, 385272 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Sh-Si, 385273 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Sha-Sho, 385274 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - She-Sho, 385275 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Shih, Hu, 1940; 385276 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Shp-Sit, 385277 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Shriver, Eunice Kennedy, 1961-1990; 385278 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Sig-Smi, 385279 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Sikorski, Dianne L., 1982-1991; 385280 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Sil-Slo, 385281 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Simon, Senator Paul, 1998, 2003; 385282 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Sinclair, Upton, 1960; 385283 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Sj-Ss, 385284 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Ska-Smy, 385285 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Sma-Sor, 385286 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Jean Kennedy, 1994-2000; 385287 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Smith, R. Harris, 1974-1992; 385288 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Smo-Sow, 385289 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Sna-Sr, 385290 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Soames, Mary, 1999; 385291 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Sorenson, Theodore, 1965-2006; 385292 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Soros, George, 1998; 385293 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Spa-Stee, 385294 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Spe-Step, 385295 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - St-Sz, 385296 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Sta-Ste, 385297 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Ste-Stez, 385298 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Ster-Stil, 385299 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Stevens, George, Jr., 1965-1994; 385300 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Stevens, John Paul, 2001; 385301 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Stevenson, Adlai, 1963-1964; 385302 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Stewart, Gretchen, 1966-1985; 385303; Schlesinger's secretary (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Sti-Sto, 385304 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Sti-Str, 385305 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Sto-Sz, 385306 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Str-Sz, 385307 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Stu-Sz, 385308 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Styron, William, 1992-2002; 385309 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Su-Sz, 385310 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Suckley, Margaret, 1966; 385311 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - T, 385312 (Box 129, Folder 6-7)
    - T-Th, 385313 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Ta-Te, 385314 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Ta-The, 385315 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Ta-Thom, 385316 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Henry J., 1962; 385317 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Th, 385318 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Theatre for Ideas, 1968-1972; 385319 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Tho-Tow, 385320 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, Hugh, 1969-1994; 385321 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Thor-Tro, 385322 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Ti-Tr, 385323 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Ti-Tz, 385324 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Tobin, Susan, 1967-1970; 385325 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Tr-Tru, 385326 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Transitional Council, 1974; 385327 (Box 132, Folder 6)